> > Brian Holt: 我们想做的第一件事就是要安装 Prettier，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: First thing here that we
wanna do is we're gonna install Prettier,
我要给你演示如何从命令行运行
and I'm gonna show you how to
run it from the command line.
所以在你的容器里，有一个叫剧本的东西。
So inside of your package.json,
there's a thing called scripts.
这里有一个叫做测试，我们还没有这个项目的测试，
Here we have one called test, which we
don't have any tests for this project yet,
所以我们什么都没有了
so we don't have anything like that.
但您可以在此处看到它会运行 echo，未指定任何测试。
But you can see here that it'll run echo,
no test specified.
所以如果我说 npm 运行测试，对吧 ?
So if I say npm run test, right?
它会在这里运行任何东西
It's gonna run whatever is in here, and
它会在没有指定测试的情况下产生回声，对吗 ?
it's gonna echo error no test specified,
right?
因此，您可以看到右侧错误，未指定测试。
So you can see right there error,
no test specified.
这就是这个剧本所针对的，它允许你放某种形式的 Bash ，或者
So that's what this script is for,
it allows you to put some sort of Bash, or
ZSH 或 PowerShell 命令在此处。
ZSH, or PowerShell command in here.
然后它会在您说 npm 运行测试或格式时运行。
And then it'll run that whenever
you say npm run test, or format, or
不管你在里面放什么
whatever you put inside of here.
所以我们可以在这里放任何东西
So we can put anything in here.
我要放一个叫格式的
I'm gonna put one called format.
>> Brian Holt: 接下来要做什么呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And what format is going
to do is it's gonna say prettier, so
它会运行这个漂亮的， >> Brian Holt:
it's gonna run this prettier,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
我们会把所有东西都放在我们的资料目录里
we're gonna run it on everything
inside of our source directory.
那么 src/，然后我们说
So src/, and then we'll say
* 我在这里有什么 ?
*., what do I have in here?
>> Brian Holt: 是， *./*.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, *./*.,
然后我们就
and then we'll put
此处 ，
here ,
就像这样
like that.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then you
actually might have to put,
>> Brian Holt: 反斜杠，例如，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Backslash, like this,
就像这样好吧
like this, okay.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这将会对任何文件运行 Prettier
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what this is gonna do is
this is going to run Prettier on any file
以及任何目录，即此 **/* 表示的内容，
and any directory,
that's what this **/* means,
具有 JS 或 HTML 扩展名的源目录的内部。
inside of the source directory that
has either a JS or an HTML extension.
你需要这里的反斜杠因为这会把它传入 Prettier
You need the backslashes here because
this'll pass it into Prettier and
它允许 Prettier 解决这一问题，而不是让 Bash 为您解决。
it allows Prettier to resolve this rather
than having Bash resolve it for you.
然后你就到这里来了
And then you come here at the end.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，如果我运行这个，它实际上是不会写的，所以
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so if I run this,
it's actually not gonna write to it, so
我应该可以说 npm 运行格式。
I should be able to say npm run format.
> > Brian Holt: 你看到它实际上是打印出来的，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And you see that
it's actually printing it out,
这不是我想要的我想让它写
which is not what I want,
I want it to actually write.
所以我们要做的就是写
So what we're gonna do here
is we're gonna say --write.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，您可以看到我有 src/app.js 和 src/index.html。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And you can see there now
I have src/app.js and src/index.html.
>> Brian Holt: 这样做很有帮助，因为您的团队中有一个人
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is helpful because
there's gonna be someone on your team that
不希望与工作流程集成。
doesn't want to integrate
with your work flow.
因此，这允许它们在落实之前直接运行此命令。
So this allows them to just run this
command right before they commit and
然后推上去，对，
then push it up, right,
因为你想让每个人都能在你的团队里阅读这份命令
because you want everyone reading
this command on your team.